[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas Lennon married this actress who is seven years his senior.", "correct_answer": "Jenny Robertson", "incorrect_answers": ["Brittany Murphy", "Kerri Kenny", "Kate Winslet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1951 Tony winner for Best Musical had its music and lyrics written by Frank Loesser and included such characters as Nathan Detroit, Miss Adelaide, and Sky Masterson?", "correct_answer": "Guys and Dolls", "incorrect_answers": ["The Pajama Game", "Carousel", "South Pacific"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these words is defined as the one unpardonable sin against ones fellows in the book The Devils Dictionary?", "correct_answer": "Success", "incorrect_answers": ["Gratitude", "Fortune", "Faith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do you call the force which slows down and stops a moving object?", "correct_answer": "Friction", "incorrect_answers": ["Gravitational force", "Magnetic force", "Molecular force"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Tyler want to do at the beginning and the end of the movie Fight Club?", "correct_answer": "Blow up the TRW and Credit Card company buildings", "incorrect_answers": ["Kill Marla", "Become the President of the United States", "Kill Jack"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The deaths caused by rhinos in India and Nepal exceed the total number of deaths caused by leopards and tigers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Eas a Chual Aluinn is the highest waterfall in this country.", "correct_answer": "Great Britain", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "China", "Sri Lanka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In most computer monitors which of these colors is not accomplished by simply emitting in the respective wavelength?", "correct_answer": "Orange", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Red", "Cyan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sir Laurence Olivier won a Razzie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What fox species is considered to be the smallest on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Fennec Fox", "incorrect_answers": ["Short-Tailed Fox", "Island Fox", "Coast Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1985 movie Pee-Wees Big Adventure, who befriends Pee-Wee and takes him up inside a  dinosaur statue to watch the sunset?", "correct_answer": "Simone", "incorrect_answers": ["Dottie", "Francis", "Large Marge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Steven Spielberg was so confident in the success of this film that he left post production to George Lucas so that he could make a different film.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]